bro4u.com 2015-08-01

# Privacy Policy - Bro4u.com

Bro4u Online Services Private Limited ("Bro4u") is concerned about the privacy of its users (hereinafter referred to as "You" "Your" "Yourself") accessing its website located at www. Bro4u.com ("Website") and has provided this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to familiarize You with the manner in which Bro4u collects, uses and discloses Your information collected through the Website.

BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT PROCEED FURTHER TO USE THIS WEBSITE.

This Privacy Policy explains how Bro4u collects personal and non-personal information, classified as mandatory or voluntary and uses, discloses and protects such information through the Website. 'Personal Information' is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person ("Personal Information"). Personal Information for the purposes of this Policy shall include, but not limited to, information regarding Your name, address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, e-mail address, etc.

You may need to provide Bro4u Your Personal Information during the course of using some services of the Bro4u, for instance, creating a User ID, provide information in Your account while registering on the Website, or provide financial information while making an online purchase, upload content, participate in any online survey or contest, communicate with Bro4u's customer service by phone, email or otherwise, provide reviews for the content available on the Website.

Bro4u collects only such Personal Information that Bro4u believes to be relevant and is required to understand You or Your interests. Bro4u collects Your Personal Information in order to record, support and facilitate Your participation in the activities You select, track Your preferences, to provide You with a customized Website experience, to notify You of any updated information and new activities and other related functions offered by Bro4u , keep You informed about latest content available on the Website, special offers, and other products and services of Bro4u , to assist You with customer service or technical support issues, to follow up with You after Your visit, to otherwise support Your relationship with Bro4u or to prevent fraud and unlawful use. 

In an effort to make our Website effective, certain information may be collected each time you visit the Website. Such information may be stored in server logs. These encrypted statistics do not identify you personally, but provide us the information regarding your visit to the Website and the type of user who is accessing our Website and certain browsing activities by You. This data may include: IP address of Your server from where the Website is being accessed, the type of browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, Safari, etc.), the operating system of Your system and the Website You last visited before visiting to our Website. The duration of Your stay on our Website is also stored in the session along with the date and time of your access. These data are used by Bro4u to understand the use and number of user visiting the Website. Some of the information related to the Website and Your visit to the Website may be shared by the sponsors, investors, advertisers, developer, strategic business partners of Bro4u and some associates in order to enhance and grow our business and the Website but we assure that these information will never include any of Your Personal Information’s. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major Websites.

When You use the Website, Bro4u's servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) may collect information indirectly and automatically about Your activities on the Website; for instance by way of cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive. This anonymous information is maintained distinctly and is not linked to the Personal Information You submit to Bro4u. 

Whether You want Your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to You. If You haven't changed Your computer's settings, most likely Your browser already accepts cookies. If You choose to decline cookies, You may not be able to fully experience all features of the Website. You can also delete Your browser cookies or disable them entirely, but this may significantly impact Your experience with the Website and may make parts of the Website non functional or inaccessible. We recommend that You leave them turned on.

We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the internet and sometimes on this Website. They may collect anonymous information about Your visits to our Website, and Your interaction with our products and services. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, address, email address, or any personally identifying information about the user.

Bro4u also uses the log file like other website servers which is the standard measures. They include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We use them to analyze trends, administer the site, track a user's movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Bro4u DOES NOT trade or sell Your Personal Information in any manner, except as specified herein or if express consent is sought from You.

Personal Information provided by You is used only:

(a) To facilitate Your use of the Website;

(b) To respond to Your inquiries or fulfill Your requests for information about the various services.

(c) To provide You with information about Bro4u's products/services and to send You information, materials, and offers from Bro4u ;

(d) To send You important information regarding the Website, changes to Bro4u's terms, conditions, and policies and/or other administrative information;

(e) To send You surveys and marketing communications that Bro4u believes may be of interest to You;

(f) To personalize Your experience on the Website and Bro4u's other websites by presenting advertising, products and offers tailored to You;

(g) To help You address Your problems with the Website including addressing any technical problems;

(h) If You purchase any content or avail of any service from the Website, to complete and fulfill Your purchase, for example, to have Your payments processed, communicate with You regarding Your purchase and provide You with related customer service;

(i) For proper administering of the Website;

(j) To conduct internal reviews and data analysis for the Website (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to specific pages within the Website);

(k) To improve the services, content and advertising on the Website;

(l) To protect the integrity of the Website; and

(m) To respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law.

You acknowledge that apart from Your Personal Information, if You upload any content on the Website, such content may contain information including Personal Information and the same may be available to the other users of the Website. Bro4u will not be liable for the disclosure and dissemination of such Personal Information to third parties. 

Bro4u may disclose aggregated information about the use of the Website, but it will never contain Personal Information. Bro4u does not disclose Personal Information to third parties in the normal course of operations. However, in situations when Bro4u is legally obligated to disclose information to the government or other third parties, Bro4u will do so.

Bro4u implements standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception of Personal Information. However, no internet site can fully eliminate security risks. 

#### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

reachus@bro4u.com
